

ANDREY PAVLYCHEV

2D/UI ARTIST

ADDRESS: Samui, Thailand PHONE: +66 (096) 236-33-10

E-MAIL: drawn.loves.you@gmail.com

WEB: http:///drawn.pro, https://dribbble.com/drawn

PROFILE

2D and User Interface artist with about 10 years experience in artwork production for mobile and social network games. I specialize in user interfaces, icon and application design. As for my competency, I have strong knowledge of Adobe Creative Suite, 2D digital drawing skills with use of Photoshop, Illustrator and Flash. Experienced in all phases of UI development, visual and technical, starting from concept up to the final design.

Being a flexible artist, I can work in a team or figure out solutions individually as well. Self-motivated and organized, able to work within established style and tight deadlines. Passionate about iconography and vector graphics.

EXPERIENCE

FREELANCE ARTIST

Samui, Thailand | January 2015 - Present

Projects include game assets, icons, app design, UI and logo design.

UI DESIGNER

KRIVORUKOFF LLP | Samui, Thailand | March 2014 — January 2015

Worked on mobile games being in charge for:

- UI restyling
- UI/UX elements wireframing, design and implementation (Unity3D NGUI Framework)
- · Animated UI pre-vis
- · Icon design

Projects: Adventure Era, Unannounced project.

2D ARTIST AND ANIMATOR

CRAZYBIT LLC | Moscow, Russia | July 2010 — March 2014

Browser, Social and Mobile game assets development. Duties included:

- · UI design and animation
- · Sprite animations sequences
- · Flash animation
- · Character skeletal animation
- Wide variety of icons (Item icons, ability icons, UI icons, app icons etc)
- · Logo design
- · Promotional materials

Projects: Lost Island, Lost Chapters, Experiment, Supernova, Hellout, WarDogs, Soldiers of Fortune, S.O.S, Metro City, Sinners, BOOM!

FLASH DESIGNER

 ${\tt IT-TERRITORY/ASTRUM-ONLINE/MAIL.RU\mid Moscow, Russia\mid December\ 2009-July\ 2010-Line (Mail.)}$

Worked on several game projects in a mixture of roles including:

- UI design/restyling
- · UI animation
- · Icon design
- In game items design
- · Character Animation

Projects: TimeZero, Juggernaut, Legends: Legacy of the Dragons, In the Hood, Cosmics: Galactic Wars, Troetsarstvie.

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

TIMEZERO LLC | Moscow, Russia | September 2007 — December 2009

Worked on a wide range of projects, from browser MMORPGs to amazing casual Flash games under Facebook and Vkontakte. Was in charge for:

- · Graphic design
- · UI design
- · Icon design
- · 2D animations for characters and FX
- · Character gear set design
- · In game items design
- · Flash banners
- · Promotional materials
- · Merchandise products design

Projects: TimeZero, Destiny Online, BUGS, Evil Tale, Crouching Panda Hidden Moose, Funny War, Dragons, Pyramid.

DESIGNER

ERA LLC | Moscow, Russia | October 2006 — August 2007

Transformed company's website to deliver more appealing interface. Managed content. Designed packaging and promotional materials.

EDUCATION

Saransk, Russia | 2002 — 2008

Area Studies Specialist, Mordovia State University

Saransk, Russia | 1996 — 2001

Pictural Art Department, Saransk State Art School #4

SKILLS

UI design, Icon design, Game items design, Logo Design, UI and Character animation (2D), Flash and GIF banners

SOFTWARE

Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop, Flash, Sketch app, Unity3D. JIRA, Redmine, Trello, GitHub. OSX